<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>ComicK - English RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/ld3z/manga-rss</link>
<description>A simple RSS feed for ComicK!</description>
<item>
    <title>Died a Slave, Reborn a Noble: Becoming the Strongest With a Daughter Who's Older Than Me (Official) - Chapter 13.2</title>
    <link>https://comick.app/comic/died-a-slave-reborn-a-noble-becoming-the-strongest-with-a-daughter-who-s-older-than-me-official</link>
    <description>Chapter 13.2 of Died a Slave, Reborn a Noble: Becoming the Strongest With a Daughter Who's Older Than Me (Official) is now available on ComicK!</description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Class no Daikirai na Joshi to Kekkon Suru Koto ni Natta - Chapter 8</title>
    <link>https://comick.app/comic/i-m-getting-married-to-a-girl-i-hate-in-my-class</link>
    <description>Chapter 8 of Class no Daikirai na Joshi to Kekkon Suru Koto ni Natta is now available on ComicK!</description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Mofumofu to Isekai Slow Life o Mezashimasu! - Chapter 6</title>
    <link>https://comick.app/comic/mofumofu-to-isekai-slow-life-o-mezashimasu</link>
    <description>Chapter 6 of Mofumofu to Isekai Slow Life o Mezashimasu! is now available on ComicK!</description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Nina Is Plotting My Death! - Chapter 21.2</title>
    <link>https://comick.app/comic/nina-is-plotting-my-death</link>
    <description>Chapter 21.2 of Nina Is Plotting My Death! is now available on ComicK!</description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>1 like produces 10 ml urine - Chapter 3</title>
    <link>https://comick.app/comic/1-like-produces-10-ml-urine</link>
    <description>Chapter 3 of 1 like produces 10 ml urine is now available on ComicK!</description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Isekai de Shippai Shinai 100 no Houhou - Chapter 1</title>
    <link>https://comick.app/comic/isekai-de-shippai-shinai-100-no-houhou-jy4p6svb</link>
    <description>Chapter 1 of Isekai de Shippai Shinai 100 no Houhou is now available on ComicK!</description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Koushaku-ke Ni Umarete Shonichi ni Atotsugi Shikkaku no Rakuin wo Osaremashitaga Kyou mo Genki ni Ikitemasu! - Chapter 4</title>
    <link>https://comick.app/comic/koushaku-ke-ni-umarete-shonichi-ni-atotsugi-shikkaku-no-rakuin-wo-osaremashitaga-kyou-mo-genki-ni-ikitemasu</link>
    <description>Chapter 4 of Koushaku-ke Ni Umarete Shonichi ni Atotsugi Shikkaku no Rakuin wo Osaremashitaga Kyou mo Genki ni Ikitemasu! is now available on ComicK!</description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
